Hello, everyone. My name is Khatmin Thant, and I am the owner and creator of Alums Declassified,
and I'm just glad that you guys are using my source to navigate through college. I'm
going to start with a little bit about myself. If you've already seen the About page, I am
a first generation college student. I'm currently attending UNC Chapel Hill in my Masters of
Educational Innovation, Technology and Entrepreneurship, or the Mighty Program. I've just been in
this city of Chapel Hill practically my entire life. I know how the city works, how higher
education works, and I just wanted to give back to the first gen students that may not
have the information that I also didn't have, and I had to figure out while navigating college
on my own. At the start, I had no idea what to do with college. I know I got in, I know
that was expected of me, but I didn't really know what to do technically. I enrolled for
my first two semesters, my freshman year, and I did 12 credit hours as a biology major,
and yeah, not even quickly, I realized at the end of the year that I was already behind.
I wasn't supposed to do 12 credit hours, but who was there to tell me about it? I didn't
know how to navigate a bunch of other stuff, trying to find specific laundry times, how
to properly grocery shop, how to work a part-time job while on college, and the financial aid
office was really seeing and hearing from me almost every week because I didn't know
how to read my financial aid package. I didn't know what a lot of it meant, and so this resource
of LUMs Declassified is here for you guys to look through. I've included my own experiences
throughout these videos and different research back practices on how you can actually navigate
college. There will include activities, there will include assignments, take your time on
it, it's completely self-paced, and at the end of the day this is meant for you, so please
study up on it and then try to apply it in your daily lives, and if you ever need, you
know, if you ever forget anything, you can always come back and look at the lessons,
look at what the site of LUMs Declassified is teaching you. I'm your alum and I'm going
to declassify the different aspects of college that I wish I knew about as a first-generation
student and hopefully helping you guys out as well. Thank you, enjoy.